- ARE YOU READY, KIDS?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all: AYE, AYE, CAPTAIN!
所有人：是，是，队长！
- I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
- 我听不到你说话。
all: AYE, AYE, CAPTAIN!
所有人：是，是，队长！
- * OHH...
-*哦...
* WHO LIVES IN A PINEAPPLE
UNDER THE SEA? *
*谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ *
all: SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS!
所有：海绵宝宝！
- * ABSORBENT AND YELLOW
AND POROUS IS HE *
- * 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的*
all: SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS!
所有：海绵宝宝！
- * IF NAUTICAL NONSENSE
BE SOMETHING YOU WISH *
- * 如果是航海废话
成为您所希望的*
all: SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS!
所有：海绵宝宝！
- * THEN DROP ON THE DECK
AND FLOP LIKE A FISH *
- * 然后掉到甲板上
像鱼一样扑腾*
all: SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS!
- READY?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
all: SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS!
所有：海绵宝宝！
SPONGEBOB SQUAREPANTS!
海绵宝宝！
- SPONGEBOB
- 海绵宝宝
SQUAREPANTS!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
*
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[energetic music]
[充满活力的音乐]
*
- A LITTLE MORE SAND.
- 再多一点沙子。
PAT, PAT, PAT.
拍，拍，拍。
PAT, PAT,
PATRICK!
帕特，帕特，
帕特里克！
CHECK IT OUT.
一探究竟。
AN EXACT REPLICA
OF THE KRUSTY KRAB.
精确复制品
甲壳蟹的。
ONE SANDY PATTY,
EXTRA GRIT.
一块沙馅饼，
额外的砂砾。
- [gulps]
A BIT DRY AND FLAVORLESS.
- [吞咽]
有点干而且无味。
I'LL TAKE TWO DOZEN.
我要两打。
- HEY, EVERYONE.
- 嘿，大家。
THE DRASTIC RADICALS
ARE TEARING IT UP
极端激进分子
正在撕毁它
ON SAND MOUNTAIN.
在沙山上。
- OH, JOHNNY, JOHNNY!
- OH, JOHNNY!
- 哦，约翰尼，约翰尼！
- 哦，约翰尼！
- LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
- 我们来看看。
- UM,
COULD YOU GIVE ME A HAND?
- 嗯，
你能帮我一下吗？
- SURE THING, BUDDY.
- 当然可以，伙计。
- [whistles]
- [口哨]
[excited chatter]
[兴奋的喋喋不休]
- I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
- 我什么也看不见。
- ALLOW ME.
- 请允许我。
[engine revs ]
[发动机转速]
[crowd gasps]
[人群喘息]
- YEAHHH!
- 是啊！
[laughs]
[笑]
- WOW.
- WHOA.
- 哇。
- 哇哦。
- WHOA.
- WOW.
- 哇哦。
- 哇。
- WOW.
- WHOA.
- 哇哦。
[bugle call]
[号角]
- [gasps]
LOOK OUT!
- [喘气]
当心！
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- SOMEONE HELP
THAT LITTLE OLD LADY!
- 有人帮忙
那个小老太太！
- HELP YOURSELVES, NIMRODS!
- 救救自己吧，宁罗德！
[rock music]
[摇滚乐]
*
[explosion]
[爆炸]
- [screaming laughter]
- [尖叫的笑声]
[engine revs ]
[发动机转速]
- JOHNNY KRILL!
- 约翰尼·克里尔！
NOT DEAD TED!
没有死！
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- GRAND MAUL GRANNY!
- 大槌奶奶！
[explosion]
[爆炸]
DRASTIC...
剧烈...
RADICALS!
激进分子！
[explosion]
[爆炸]
THE DRASTICALS!
激进派！
- DID YOU SEE THAT?
- 你看到了吗？
both: WHAT WAS THAT?
两人：那是什么？
- WHY, THOSE AWE
THE DWASTIC WADICALS,
- 为什么，那些敬畏
DWASTIC WADICALS，
THE NUMBEW ONE PWACTITIONERS
OF EXTWEME SPOWTS.
排名第一的参与者
EXTWEME 景点。
[slurps]
[啜饮]
both: EXTREME WHAT?
两者：极端什么？
- EXTREME SPOWTS...
- 极限点...
- EXTREME SPOTS?
- 极端地点？
WELL, THAT'S NO FAIR.
嗯，这不公平。
YOU'RE ALREADY COVERED
IN EXTREME SPOTS.
您已经得到保障
在极端地点。
OOH.
HOLD ON A SECOND.
哦。
请稍等。
[hive buzzing]
[蜂巢嗡嗡声]
[screaming,
electricity crackling]
[尖叫，
电噼啪声]
OKAY, LET'S GO MEET
OUR NEW HEROES.
好的，我们去见面吧
我们的新英雄。
[laughing]
[笑]
- WE WANT TO JOIN
YOUR EXTREME SPOTS TEAM.
- 我们想加入
您的极限地点团队。
AS YOU CAN SEE,
WE'RE ALSO COVERED HEAD TO TOE
如您所见，
我们也从头到脚都做好了防护
IN THE MOST EXTREME OF SPOTS.
在最极端的地方。
- ITCHY SPOTS.
- 发痒的地方。
[all cackling]
[全都咯咯笑]
- YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
- 你在开玩笑吧。
- OH, NO.
OH, NO, STOP.
- 哦，不。
哦，不，停下来。
STOP.
[laughs]
停止。
[笑]
EXTREME SPOTS.
[laughs]
极端地点。
[笑]
IT'S EXTREME "SPORTS,"
NOT "SPOTS."
这是极限“运动”，
不是“斑点”。
SO, YOU WANT TO BE
A DRASTICAL?
所以，你想成为
激进的？
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT,
LITTLE DUDE.
让我们看看你得到了什么，
小家伙。
- NO PROBLEMO.
- 没问题。
I GUESS YOU JUST HOP UP
LIKE THIS...
我猜你只是跳起来
像这样...
[engine revs ]
[发动机转速]
[tires screech]
[轮胎尖叫声]
HEY!
嘿！
COME BACK!
回来！
[engine revs ]
[发动机转速]
HEY!
嘿！
[screams]
[尖叫声]
OH!
哦！
[groans]
[呻吟]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
YOUR TURN, FAT BOY.
轮到你了，胖男孩。
- HEY, HOW'D WE GET UP HERE?
- 嘿，我们怎么到这里来？
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[gulps]
[吞咽]
[seal barks]
[海豹吠叫]
[horn honks]
[喇叭鸣响]
[dolphin whistles]
[海豚哨声]
[crash]
[碰撞]
[duck quacks]
[鸭子嘎嘎叫]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[thud]
OOH!
[砰]
哦！
- OUR SPORTS ARE TOO EXTREME
FOR YOU DUDES.
- 我们的运动太极限了
为了你们伙计们。
MAYBE WE SHOULD START YOU TWO
ON SOMETHING EASIER.
也许我们应该让你们两个开始
做一些更简单的事情。
WHAT GAMES DO YOU DUDES
LIKE TO PLAY?
你们都玩什么游戏
喜欢玩吗？
- OH, I KNOW.
- 哦，我知道。
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE SOMETHING
CALLED JUMP ROPE?
来一点怎么样
叫跳绳？
- JUMP ROPE, EH?
DEMONSTRATE.
- 跳绳，呃？
证明。
- READY, PATRICK?
- 准备好了吗，帕特里克？
ON YOUR MARK, GET SET,
各就各位，准备好，
JUMP ROPE!
跳绳！
- EXTREME!
- 极端！
HEY, WHO'S HOLDING
THE OTHER END?
嘿，谁在持有
另一端？
- I AM, OF COURSE.
- 我是，当然。
- WHOA.
- HI, PATRICK.
- 哇哦。
- 嗨，帕特里克。
- AH.
- 啊。
[plays harmonica]
[吹口琴]
* MY BEST FRIEND IS SPONGEBOB
- SING IT.
* 我最好的朋友是海绵宝宝
- 唱吧。
- * HE HAS A SQUARE HEAD
- YEAH!
- * 他有一个方头
- 是啊！
- * I TRY ON HIS CLOTHES
WHILE HE'S ASLEEP IN BED *
- * 我试穿他的衣服
当他在床上睡着时*
- WOW--WHAT?
- 哇——什么？
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
IT'S WEIRD.
这很奇怪。
MY FACE IS LEAKING.
我的脸漏水了。
- YOUR FACE ISN'T LEAKING.
- 你的脸没有漏水。
YOU'RE JUST SWEATING
FROM ALL THE EXERCISE.
你只是出汗了
来自所有的锻炼。
- EXERCISE?
- 锻炼？
OOH, I DIDN'T SIGN UP
FOR THIS.
哦，我没有注册
为此。
[pants]
OH.
[裤子]
哦。
- EXTREME.
- 极端。
- DUDE, THAT WAS NOT EXTREME.
- 老兄，这并不极端。
NOW LET THE DRASTICALS
SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
现在让激进分子
向您展示它是如何完成的。
GRAB IT, GRANNY.
抓住它，奶奶。
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
DRASTICALS! WOW!
激进派！哇！
YEAH!
是的！
- KICK IT UP A NOTCH.
- 更上一层楼。
both: OOH.
两人：哦。
- YEAH!
- 是的！
[thud]
[砰]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[small explosion]
[小爆炸]
- YEAH!
SEE?
- 是的！
看？
EXTREME SPORTS
SHOULD BE EXPLOSIVE. BOOM!
极限运动
应该是爆炸性的。繁荣！
- EXPLOSIVE, HUH?
I KNOW JUST THE THING.
- 爆炸，嗯？
我只知道这件事。
[inhales]
[吸气]
[blows air]
[吹气]
BOOM!
繁荣！
- POW!
- KAZAM!
- 战俘！
- 卡赞！
- BLOOEY!
- WHOOSH!
- 哎呀！
- 嗖嗖！
- BIFF!
- IMPRESSED?
- 比夫！
- 印象深刻吗？
all: NO.
全体：没有。
- LOOK, DUDES.
- 看，伙计们。
TO BE EXTREME,
YOU GOT TO GO BIGGER.
变得极端，
你必须做得更大。
SHOW 'EM, DRASTICALS.
让他们看看，激进派。
[rock music]
[摇滚乐]
[splashing]
[溅]
*
WATCH THIS.
注意这个。
[engine revs ]
[发动机转速]
- HOLY CHUM!
- 天哪！
[panicked screaming]
[惊慌尖叫]
[engine revs ]
[发动机转速]
[crash]
[碰撞]
- EXTREME.
- 极端。
HUP.
HUP。
胡普。
NOW THAT'S
HOW YOU DO EXTREME.
现在就是这样
你如何做到极限。
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
你明白吗？
- I THINK I DO.
IS FIGHTING EXTREME?
- 我想我愿意。
战斗是否极端？
- FIGHTING IS TOTALLY EXTREME.
- 战斗完全是极端的。
- I WANT A CLEAN FIGHT.
- 我想要一场干净的战斗。
I DON'T WANT TO SEE ANY TRASH
LAYING AROUND.
我不想看到任何垃圾
躺在周围。
[groans]
[呻吟]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
WHOA!
哇啊！
[muffled screaming]
[低沉的尖叫声]
- OH...
- 哦...
WE GIVE UP!
FLING.
我们放弃！
一扔。
[birds chirping]
[鸟鸣声]
THAT WAS CLOSE.
- NOT SO FAST.
已经很接近了。
- 没那么快。
THAT'S NOT FIGHTING.
这不是打架。
STAND ASIDE.
站到一边。
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
我将向您展示它是如何完成的。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[machine rumbles]
[机器隆隆声]
- NO!
IT'S DRY CLEAN-ONLY.
- 不！
只能干洗。
[rumbling]
[隆隆声]
[crash]
[碰撞]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
[weakly]
AVENGE ME.
[微弱]
为我报仇。
[moans]
OH.
[呻吟声]
哦。
- OH.
- BRUTAL.
- 哦。
- 残酷。
- CHARLIE?
- 查理？
[growls]
[咆哮]
[birds chirping]
[鸟鸣声]
- OOH.
- EVEN MORE BRUTAL!
-哦。
- 更加残酷！
- NOW THAT WAS EXTREME, DUDES.
- 现在这太极端了，伙计们。
YOU THINK YOU'RE STARTING
TO GET IT?
你认为你正在开始
想要得到它吗？
- OH, YEAH.
- YEAH.
- 哦，是的。
- 是的。
- SO WHAT ELSE YOU GOT?
- 那你还有什么？
- HMM, THERE IS ONE SPORT
- 嗯，只有一项运动
THAT PATRICK'S AN EXPERT AT.
帕特里克是这方面的专家。
- DUMPSTER DIVING!
- 垃圾箱潜水！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[groaning]
[呻吟]
WHOA, WHOA--
哇，哇——
- HOORAY!
- 万岁！
[squishy sounds]
[吱吱作响的声音]
- [coughs]
- [咳嗽]
- THAT'S NOT EXTREME.
- 这并不极端。
- [coughs]
- [咳嗽]
HOW REVOLTING.
多么令人反感。
A-BRUSH, BRUSH, BRUSH, BRUSH,
BRUSH, BRUSH, BRUSH, BRUSH.
A-刷子，刷子，刷子，刷子，
刷，刷，刷，刷。
- OKAY, THAT'S KIND OF EXTREME.
NOT BAD.
- 好吧，这有点极端。
不错。
BUT THE DRASTICALS
WILL SHOW YOU HOW IT'S DONE.
但激进派
将向您展示它是如何完成的。
[rock music]
[摇滚乐]
*
- RIGHT.
- 正确的。
OKAY, ARTIFICIAL HIP,
DON'T FAIL ME NOW.
好的，人工髋关节，
现在别让我失望。
- OH.
- OOH.
- 哦。
-哦。
[crash]
[碰撞]
- [cackles]
- [咯咯笑]
EXTREME!
极端！
- THAT IS ONE TOUGH
ELDERLY PERSON.
- 这是一项艰巨的任务
老人。
- DUDES, THAT WAS AWESOME.
- 伙计们，太棒了。
WHAT OTHER CRAZY SPORTS
DO YOU TWO PLAY?
还有什么疯狂的运动
你们两个玩吗？
- WELL,
THERE IS A VERY EXTREMELY
- 嗯，
有一种非常极端的
EXTREME SPORT WE PLAY
IF YOU'RE UP TO IT.
我们玩的极限运动
如果你能做到的话。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- HEY, WHERE ARE
THE DRASTICALS?
- 嘿，在哪里
激进派？
[engine revving]
[发动机转速]
HERE THEY COME!
他们来了！
- [laughs]
- [笑]
AH! YEAH!
啊！是的！
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- WOW.
- AMAZING.
- 哇。
- 惊人的。
- JELLYFISHING, YEAH!
- 捕水母，是的！
[electricity crackles]
[电流爆裂声]
[explosion]
[爆炸]
- DUDES, NOW WE GET IT.
- 伙计们，现在我们明白了。
THESE SPOTS ARE WAY EXTREME.
这些地方太极端了。
- AND ITCHY.
- 而且很痒。
- AS YOU CAN SEE,
- 如你看到的，
EXTWEME SPOTS AWE THE DIWECT
BY-PWODUCT
EXTWEME 景点让您惊叹不已
副产品
OF THE MOST EXTWEME SPOWTS.
最极端的景点之一。
- WHO IS THAT GUY?
- 那个人是谁？